proletariat.com 2019-03-23

# PrivacyPolicy

Revision Date: May 24, 2018

Proletariat knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly.  This notice describes our privacy policy for Proletariat’s games (such as Streamline and World Zombination) and Proletariat’s websites, such as the proletariat.com web site as well as the game specific websites operated by Proletariat such as playstreamline.com, streamote.tv, and worldzombination.com (the “Properties”).  

This privacy policy is current as of the revision date noted above. Please note that this policy may be amended from time to time to reflect changes and additions to the privacy policy. Please check back for the most current version before relying on any of the provisions in this privacy policy.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact the Community team by emailing helpme@proletariat.com.

This privacy policy covers only information that is collected through the Properties.

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our service to make your experience safer and easier. We only collect personal information about you that we consider necessary for achieving this purpose. 

In general, you can browse the Properties without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are no longer anonymous to us. 

## Information We Collect About Anonymous Visitors

We automatically track certain information based upon your behavior on certain of our Properties. We use this information to do internal research on our users’ demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand, protect and serve you and our community.

### Log Files

Like many Web sites, we automatically gather certain information about traffic on our Properties and store it in log files.  This information includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.  We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the Properties, to track users’ movements around the Properties and to gather demographic information about our user base.  

We link this automatically collected data to personally identifiable information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes.  We use cookies on certain of our Properties.  As noted above, we link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our Properties.  This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by the Properties only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

We use both session ID and persistent cookies.

A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our Properties.

A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file.

[We use cookies to keep track of authentication information and user state.

 If you reject cookies, you may still use our Properties, but your ability to use some areas of our Properties will be limited.

 Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our Properties.  We have no access to or control over these cookies. See “Third Party Advertisers.”

### Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)

We employ a software technology called clear gifs, also referred to as web beacons or web bugs, that help manage content on the Properties by tracking what content is effective.  Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users.  In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information. 

We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails recipients have opened.  This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.  If you would like to opt-out of these emails, please see “Choice and Opt-out.”

## Information We Collect To Respond To Your Choices and Requests

### Registration

In order to use some features of our Properties, you must first complete the registration form and create a user name and password.  During registration you are required to give truthful contact information (such as name and email address) in accordance with our terms of use http://proletariat.com/tos. We use this information to contact you about the services on our Properties in which you have expressed interest.  

### Surveys or Contests

We may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests or surveys on one or more of our Properties.  If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you.  The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address) and demographic information.  

We use this information to notify contest winners and award prizes, to monitor Property traffic, or to personalize our Properties (in the case of anonymous information collected in surveys) and to send participants an email newsletter.

We may use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys or contests. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a contest or survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice.

### Chat Rooms, Forums and Messages

If you choose to post messages in our chat rooms, forums or other public message areas or leave feedback for other users, we will collect the information you post. We retain this information as necessary to resolve disputes, provide customer support and troubleshoot problems as permitted by law.

Any information that is disclosed in chat, forums or bulletin boards should be considered public information, and users who message one another may not know each other personally. If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Properties, we may collect such information into a file specific to you.  We reserve the right to terminate the accounts of visitors who use these services in a manner inconsistent with the terms of use  http://proletariat.com/tos.

## Communication from Us or the Properties

### Special Offers and Updates

We will occasionally send information on products, services, special deals, and promotions to our users. We give users the option to receive promotional email communications from us. You may opt out of these communications. Instructions for discontinuing receipt of promotional email communications from us will be provided in email communications to users. 

### Newsletters

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you.  Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe.  Please see the “Choice and Opt-out” section.

### Profile 

We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, and/or third party sources to create a “profile” of your preferences.  We tie your personally identifiable information, and your purchasing history, to information in the profile, in order to provide tailored promotions and marketing offers and to improve the content of the Properties for you.  

We do not share your profile with other third parties.

## Conditions Under Which We Share Information

### Aggregate Information (Non-Personally Identifiable)

We share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our partners and advertisers.  This information does not identify individual users. 

### Personally Identifiable Information

Except as discussed below, we do not share Personally Identifiable Information with Third Parties. 

### Third Party Advertisers

The ads appearing on Properties are delivered to users by our advertising partner(s).   We share Web site usage information about users with our advertising partner for the purpose of targeting our Internet banner advertisements on our Properties. 

Our advertising partner may use cookies and clear GIFs on the Properties, which allow it to recognize a user’s cookie when a user visits the Properties. The information that our advertising partner collects and shares through this technology is not personally identifiable.  

For more information about our third-party advertiser, or to learn more about the choices available to you regarding this anonymous information, please contact the Community team by emailing helpme@proletariat.com.

### Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights; to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on us or one of our Properties; or in connection with an actual or proposed corporate transaction or insolvency proceeding involving all or part of the business or asset to which the information pertains.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at helpme@proletariat.com. 

The Properties may contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by us. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy policies of such other sites.  Such third party sites may collect personally identifiable information about users when users visit their websites. Third party publishers may also collect personally identifiable information as a requirement of accessing their games or content. This privacy policy does not extend to external websites and companies or third party publishers with links to or from our Properties or who collect personally identifiable information through their games available on one of our Properties. Please refer directly to these companies and websites regarding their privacy policies

We encourage you to be aware when you leave a Property and to read the privacy policies of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.  

This privacy policy applies only to information collected by the Properties. 

We will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from any person under the age of 13. We encourage parents to instruct their children to never give out personal information when online. Parents who are concerned about the transfer of personal information from their children may contact us.

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our services, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at helpme@proletariat.com. We may decline requests that are unreasonably repetitive, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or are extremely impractical.

The security of your personal information is important to us.  When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our registration page, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).  

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.  No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.  Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Properties, you can email us at helpme@proletariat.com.

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: helpme@proletariat.com.

--

1" = "1" "ActiveUS 156481942v.2" "" ActiveUS 156481942v.2
